redux a single source of truth for all the data in your javascript application
redux 是javascript 应用程序中所有数据的单一事实来源
modern web applications are represented as a complex tree of components
现代 Web 应用程序被表示为一个复杂的组件树，这些
components that constantly produce and share data called state and when state
组件不断产生和共享称为状态的数据，当
is decentralized it can become difficult to understand and test redux is both a
状态分散时，它可能变得难以理解和测试 redux 既是 一个
pattern and library that helps developers implement complex state
模式和库，可帮助开发人员大规模实现复杂的状态
management requirements at scale it was created by dan abramov and andrew clark
管理需求它由 facebook 的 dan abramov 和 andrew clark 创建
at facebook and is one of the most loved and hated libraries in the react
，是 react 生态系统中最受欢迎和最讨厌的库之一，
ecosystem it relies on a single immutable object to store all of the
它依赖于单个不可变对象来存储所有
application state kind of like a client-side database to change the state
应用程序状态有点像客户端数据库来更改状态，
like when a button is clicked an action will be dispatched which has a name like
例如单击按钮时将调度一个动作，该动作的名称
an event and a payload with the data that it wants to change remember the
类似于事件和带有要更改的数据的有效负载记住
store is immutable so to change the state of the application an entirely new
存储是不可变的，所以 要更改应用程序的状态，
object is created by passing the current state and the action payload into a
通过传递当前状态和操作负载 i 创建一个全新的对象 nto 一个
reducer function which returns a new object with the entire application state
reducer 函数，它返回一个包含整个应用程序状态的新对象，
the end result is a one-way data flow that is predictable and testable and it
最终结果是一个可预测和可测试的单向数据流，
also opens the door to awesome dev tools that allow you to time travel through
它还为令人敬畏的开发工具打开了大门，允许
your application's data but it comes at a cost of additional boilerplate code
您在应用程序的数据中进行时间旅行，但是 它是以额外的样板代码为代价的，
that might add too much complexity to a smaller project to get started create a
这可能会给较小的项目增加太多的复杂性，以便开始
react app with your favorite tool then install the redux toolkit first use
使用您最喜欢的工具创建一个反应应用程序，然后安装 redux 工具包首先使用
configure store to set up the global store object which will register any
配置商店来设置全局商店对象，该对象将注册任何
reducers defined elsewhere in the code then provider will make its data
在代码中其他地方定义的减速器，然后提供者将使其数据
accessible to the entire component tree next create a slice like pizza to
可供整个组件树访问接下来创建一个像披萨一样的切片来
represent some data in the store it should have a unique name and initial
表示存储中的一些数据它应该有一个唯一的名称和初始
state but most importantly it contains a collection of reducers which are
状态，但最重要的是它包含一个减速器的集合， 是
functions that take the old state and an action then define the logic required to
采用旧状态和操作的函数，然后定义更改状态所需的逻辑
change the state redux toolkit will automatically generate actions that
redux 工具包将自动 生成
correspond to the names of these reducer functions we can export them then put
与这些 reducer 函数名称对应的操作，我们可以将它们导出，然后将
them to use in an actual ui component the beauty of redux is that we can
它们用于实际的 ui 组件redux 的美妙之处在于我们可以
select data anywhere in the application without the need for context or prop
在应用程序的任何位置选择数据，而无需上下文或道具
drilling instead we can grab any reactive value or slice in the store
钻取，而是我们可以 现在使用 use 选择器钩子获取存储中的任何反应值或切片以
with the use selector hook now to change the application's data an action needs
更改应用程序的数据
to be dispatched to the store that can be accomplished with the use dispatch
需要将操作分派到存储区，这可以通过使用分派钩子完成，
hook which might send an action name and data payload on a normal browser event
这可能会在正常情况下发送操作名称和数据有效负载 浏览器事件（
like a button click now serve the application and install the redux
例如单击按钮）现在为应用程序提供服务并安装 redux
devtools browser extension unlike a normal project you're able to inspect
devtools 浏览器扩展 与普通项目不同，您可以检查
and debug the entire timeline of actions and state changes in your application
和调试应用程序中动作和状态更改的整个时间线
this has been redux in 100 seconds upgrade to fireship pro if you want to
这已经在 100 秒内完成了 redux升级到 fireship 亲，如果您想以
learn all kinds of other react concepts in a format like this thanks for
这样的格式学习各种其他 React 概念，谢谢
watching and i will see you in the next one
观看，我会在下一个